<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xml" href="https://dorothybrooks.github.io/feed.xslt.xml"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><generator uri="http://jekyllrb.com" version="3.3.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://dorothybrooks.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://dorothybrooks.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2016-12-08T19:02:40-08:00</updated><id>https://dorothybrooks.github.io//</id><title type="html">The Journey of Grief</title><author><name>{&quot;name&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;email&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;uri&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;bio&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;twitter&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;github&quot;=&gt;nil}</name></author><entry><title type="html">10 Things I Learned from Running Grief Camps</title><link href="https://dorothybrooks.github.io/blog/2016/Oct/post-4/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="10 Things I Learned from Running Grief Camps" /><published>2016-10-12T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2016-10-12T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>https://dorothybrooks.github.io/blog/2016/Oct/post-4</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://dorothybrooks.github.io/blog/2016/Oct/post-4/">&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Oh, yes; there are thousands,&amp;rdquo; she replied. &amp;ldquo;Then send for them all to come here as soon as possible, and let each one bring a long piece of string.&amp;rdquo; The Queen turned to the mice that attended her and told them to go at once and get all her people.  As soon as they heard her orders they ran away in every direction as fast as possible. &amp;ldquo;Now,&amp;rdquo; said the Scarecrow to the Tin Woodman, &amp;ldquo;you must go to those trees by the riverside and make a truck that will carry the Lion.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So the Woodman went at once to the trees and began to work; and he soon made a truck out of the limbs of trees, from which he chopped away all the leaves and branches.  He fastened it together with wooden pegs and made the four wheels out of short pieces of a big tree trunk.  So fast and so well did he work that by the time the mice began to arrive the truck was all ready for them. They came from all directions, and there were thousands of them: big mice and little mice and middle-sized mice; and each one brought a piece of string in his mouth.  It was about this time that Dorothy woke from her long sleep and opened her eyes.  She was greatly astonished to find herself lying upon the grass, with thousands of mice standing around and looking at her timidly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But the Scarecrow told her about everything, and turning to the dignified little Mouse, he said: &amp;ldquo;Permit me to introduce to you her Majesty, the Queen.&amp;rdquo; Dorothy nodded gravely and the Queen made a curtsy, after which she became quite friendly with the little girl. The Scarecrow and the Woodman now began to fasten the mice to the truck, using the strings they had brought.  One end of a string was tied around the neck of each mouse and the other end to the truck.  Of course the truck was a thousand times bigger than any of the mice who were to draw it; but when all the mice had been harnessed, they were able to pull it quite easily.  Even the Scarecrow and the Tin Woodman could sit on it, and were drawn swiftly by their queer little horses to the place where the Lion lay asleep. After a great deal of hard work, for the Lion was heavy, they managed to get him up on the truck.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then the Queen hurriedly gave her people the order to start, for she feared if the mice stayed among the poppies too long they also would fall asleep. At first the little creatures, many though they were, could hardly stir the heavily loaded truck; but the Woodman and the Scarecrow both pushed from behind, and they got along better.  Soon they rolled the Lion out of the poppy bed to the green fields, where he could breathe the sweet, fresh air again, instead of the poisonous scent of the flowers. Dorothy came to meet them and thanked the little mice warmly for saving her companion from death.  She had grown so fond of the big Lion she was glad he had been rescued. Then the mice were unharnessed from the truck and scampered away through the grass to their homes.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Queen of the Mice was the last to leave. &amp;ldquo;If ever you need us again,&amp;rdquo; she said, &amp;ldquo;come out into the field and call, and we shall hear you and come to your assistance.  Good-bye!&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Good-bye!&amp;rdquo; they all answered, and away the Queen ran, while Dorothy held Toto tightly lest he should run after her and frighten her. After this they sat down beside the Lion until he should awaken; and the Scarecrow brought Dorothy some fruit from a tree near by, which she ate for her dinner. It was some time before the Cowardly Lion awakened, for he had lain among the poppies a long while, breathing in their deadly fragrance; but when he did open his eyes and roll off the truck he was very glad to find himself still alive. &amp;ldquo;I ran as fast as I could,&amp;rdquo; he said, sitting down and yawning, &amp;ldquo;but the flowers were too strong for me.  How did you get me out?&amp;rdquo; Then they told him of the field mice, and how they had&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>{&quot;name&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;email&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;uri&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;bio&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;twitter&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;github&quot;=&gt;nil}</name></author><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://source.unsplash.com/anV_zgNDZhc" /></entry><entry><title type="html">3 Ways to Help with Grief</title><link href="https://dorothybrooks.github.io/blog/2016/Oct/post-3/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="3 Ways to Help with Grief" /><published>2016-10-10T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2016-10-10T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>https://dorothybrooks.github.io/blog/2016/Oct/post-3</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://dorothybrooks.github.io/blog/2016/Oct/post-3/">&lt;p&gt;Now, one of the peculiar characteristics of the savage in his domestic hours, is his wonderful patience of industry.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>{&quot;name&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;email&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;uri&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;bio&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;twitter&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;github&quot;=&gt;nil}</name></author><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://source.unsplash.com/MApzyeDS-gM" /></entry><entry><title type="html">The Best Thing You Can Do for Your Child</title><link href="https://dorothybrooks.github.io/blog/2016/Oct/post-2/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Best Thing You Can Do for Your Child" /><published>2016-10-09T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2016-10-09T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>https://dorothybrooks.github.io/blog/2016/Oct/post-2</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://dorothybrooks.github.io/blog/2016/Oct/post-2/">&lt;p&gt;Now, one of the peculiar characteristics of the savage in his domestic hours, is his wonderful patience of industry.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>{&quot;name&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;email&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;uri&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;bio&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;twitter&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;github&quot;=&gt;nil}</name></author><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://source.unsplash.com/0A_b9G-Rm6w" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Remembering Your Loved One Today and Tomorrow</title><link href="https://dorothybrooks.github.io/blog/2016/Oct/post-1/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Remembering Your Loved One Today and Tomorrow" /><published>2016-10-08T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2016-10-08T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>https://dorothybrooks.github.io/blog/2016/Oct/post-1</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://dorothybrooks.github.io/blog/2016/Oct/post-1/">&lt;p&gt;Now, one of the peculiar characteristics of the savage in his domestic hours, is his wonderful patience of industry.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>{&quot;name&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;email&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;uri&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;bio&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;twitter&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;github&quot;=&gt;nil}</name></author><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://source.unsplash.com/VfUN94cUy4o" /></entry></feed>
